A Guide to the Records of the Drug Policy Office of XXX, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Grants, 1990-1994., Extent:.
  - DARE, Franklin County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Frederick County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Galax, 1991
  - DARE, Greene County, 1992
  - DARE, Greensville County, 1991-1992
  - DARE, Halifax County, 1993
  - DARE, Hanover County, 1991-1992
  - DARE, Highland County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Hopewell, 1993
  - DARE, Lancaster County, 1992
  - DARE, Leesburg, 1992
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1991
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1992
  - DARE, Lunenburg County, 1993
  - DARE, Manassas, 1989-1990
  - DARE, Manassas, 1991-1992
  - DARE, Marion, 1991
  - DARE, Mathews County, 1992
  - DARE, Middlesex County, 1992
  - DARE, Nelson County, 1992
  - DARE, Newport News, 1991
  - DARE, Newport News, 1992
  - DARE, Newport News, 1993 (Folder 1-3)
  - DARE, Norfolk, 1993
  - DARE, Norton, 1992
  - DARE, Orange County, 1992
  - DARE, Page County, 1991
  - DARE, Page County, 1992
  - DARE, Petersburg, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Poquoson, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Powhatan County, 1991
  - DARE, Prince Edward County, 1992
  - DARE, Prince George County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Prince William County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Pulaski County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Rappahannock County, 1991
  - DARE, Roanoke City, 1993
  - DARE, Roanoke County, 1991
  - DARE, Salem, 1993
  - DARE, Scott County, 1993
  - DARE, Smyth County, 1991
  - DARE, Spotsylvania County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Stafford County, 1991 (Folder 1-2)
  - DARE, Staunton, 1991-1992
  - DARE, Suffolk, 1993
  - DARE, Tazewell County, 1991
  - DARE, Tazewell County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Vienna, 1992
  - DARE, Virginia Beach, 1991
  - DARE, Warren County, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Washington County, 1991
  - DARE, Williamsburg-James City County, 1991
  - DARE, Winchester, 1992
  - DARE, Wise County, 1993
  - DARE, Wythe County, 1991
  - DARE, Wytheville, 1992
  - DARE, York County, 1991
  - DARE, York County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Department of Education, 1990-1991
  - DARE, Department of State Police, 1988-1990
  - DARE, Department of State Police, 1991-1993
  - Eastern Shore Community Service Board, 1987-1990
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1988-1989
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1989-1990
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System, 1989-1990
  - Educational and Training Communications, 1991-1992
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Alexandria Public Schools, 1989-1991
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Alexandria Public Schools, 1991-1993
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Danville Public Schools, 1991-1992 (Folder 1-2)
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Norfolk Public Schools, 1991
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Petersburg Public Schools, 1991
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Portsmouth Public Schools, 1991
  - Emergency Grants to Schools, Richmond Public Schools, 1991-1992
  - Fairfax County YMCA, 1990-1991
  - Family Services of Norfolk, 1988-1989
  - Family Services of Norfolk, 1989-1991
  - Family Services of Tidewater, 1990-1991
  - Five Rivers Regional Educational Service, 1989-1990
  - FOCUS Women's Resource Center (Charlottesville, Va.), 1991
  - Girls, Inc., of Tidewater, 1992
  - George Mason Junior-Senior High School (Falls Church, Va.), 1990-1991
  - George Mason University, 1989-1992
  - GRIP, 1987-1990
  - Halifax County Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Hampton Police Division, 1989-1992 (Folder 1-5)
  - Hampton University, 1989-1990
  - Hanover County Community Service Board, 1988-1991
  - Harrisonburg-Rockingham Community Service Board, 1987-1989
  - Henrico County, Essex Village, 1991
  - Henrico County Public Schools, 1989-1991
  - Henrico Area Mental Health Mental Retardation Services, 1989-1991
  - Hopkins House Association, Inc. (Alexandria, Va.), 1990-1991
  - IDEA, Alexandria, 1991
  - IDEA, Arlington County, 1991
  - IDEA, Arlington County, 1993
  - IDEA, Ashland, 1991
  - IDEA, Bedford city, 1991
  - IDEA, Bristol, 1991
  - IDEA, Essex County, 1991
  - IDEA, Franklin County, 1991
  - IDEA, Fredericksburg, 1991
  - IDEA, Fredericksburg, 1993
  - IDEA, Giles County, 1991
  - IDEA, Giles County, 1993
  - IDEA, Halifax and Mecklenburg County, 1991
  - IDEA, Hampton, 1991
  - IDEA, Hanover County, 1991
  - IDEA, Hanover County, 1993
  - IDEA, Henrico County, 1991
  - IDEA, James City County, 1991
  - IDEA, Lancaster County, 1991
  - IDEA, Lynchburg, 1991
  - IDEA, Manassas, 1991
  - IDEA, Martinsville, 1991
  - IDEA, Martinsville, 1993
  - IDEA, Newport News, 1991
  - IDEA, Newport News, 1993
  - IDEA, Norfolk, 1991
  - IDEA, Norfolk, 1993
  - IDEA, North Central Virginia Regional Narcotics Task Force, 1991
  - IDEA, Northwest Virginia Drug Task Force, 1991
  - IDEA, Norton, 1991
  - IDEA, Norton, 1993
  - IDEA, Petersburg, 1991
  - IDEA, Petersburg, 1993
  - IDEA, Pittsylvania County, 1991
  - IDEA, Portsmouth, 1991
  - IDEA, Portsmouth, 1993
  - IDEA, Pulaski, 1991
  - IDEA, Richmond (city), 1991
  - IDEA, Richmond (city), 1993
  - IDEA, Winchester, 1991
  - King George County Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Lee County Office on Youth-District One, Inc., 1987-1991
  - Lee County Office on Youth-District One, Inc., 1990-1991
  - Lonesome Pine Office on Youth (Wise County, Va.), 1988-1989
  - Lonesome Pine Office on Youth (Wise County, Va.), 1989-1991
  - Loudoun County Youth Shelter, 1989-1991
  - Love Outreach Center (Richmond, Va.), 1991
  - Lynchburg City Public Schools, 1987-1988
  - Lynchburg City Public Schools, 1988-1989
  - Lynchburg YMCA, 1990
  - Mental Health Services of the Roanoke Valley, 1991
  - Mothers Inc., 1990-1992
  - National Association of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors (NAADAC), 1992
  - National Collegiate Conference, 1993
  - Newport News Public Schools, 1988-1989
  - Newport News Public Schools, 1990-1991
  - Newport News 7th District Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court 1991
  - Newport News Police Department, 1993
  - Newport News Safe Neighborhoods Coalition, 1991-1993
  - Norfolk Community Against Drug Related Activities (CADRA)/Community Drug Intervention Program (CDIP), 1991-1992
  - Norfolk Community Against Drug Related Activities (CADRA)/Community Drug Intervention Program (CDIP), 1993
  - Norfolk Community Services Board, 1987-1990
  - Northampton-Accomack County, Big Brothers Big Sisters, 1989-1991
  - "Parents, Kids, Drugs", Live broadcast, 1991-1993
  - Parents Support Center, 1989-1990
  - Patrick Henry Drug and Alcohol Council, 1988-1989
  - People, Inc., of Southwest Virginia, 1987-1988
  - People, Inc., of Southwest Virginia, 1988-1990
  - Petersburg Redevelopment and Housing Authority, 1991
  - Portsmouth Community Service Board, 1987-1988
  - Portsmouth Community Service Board, 1988-1990
  - Portsmouth City Department Parks and Recreation, 1990
  - Prince William County Community Services Board, Big Friends, 1987-1989
  - Prince William County Community Services Board, New Horizons, 1988-1990
  - Project LINK, College of William and Mary, 1991
  - Project LINK, Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Substance Abuse Services, 1991-1992
  - Project LINK, Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Substance Abuse Services, 1993
  - Project LINK, Region Ten Community Service Board, 1991
  - Project LINK, Virginia Beach Community Service Board, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Inc., 1991-1993
  - PULSAR, Albemarle County, 1991
  - PULSAR, Augusta County, 1991
  - PULSAR, Bedford County, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Culpeper County, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Greene County, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Madison County, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Newport News, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Norfolk, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Petersburg, 1991
  - PULSAR, Richmond, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Tazewell County, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Virginia Beach, 1991-1992
  - PULSAR, Waynesboro, 1991
  - PULSAR, Winchester, 1991
  - Richmond, Human Services Policy Analyst, 1991
  - Richmond Community Services Board, 1991-1992
  - Richmond City Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Richmond Youth Services Commission, 1993
  - Roanoke City Public Schools, 1987-1988
  - Roanoke County Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Robert E. Lee High School (Staunton, Va.), 1988-1990
  - Rockbridge Area Community Services Board, 1988-1990
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Accomack-Northampton Counties, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Buchanan County, 1993
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Buckingham County, 1993
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charles Cit County, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charles City County, 1994-1995
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charlotte County, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Franklin County, 1993
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Giles County, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Giles County, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Halifax County, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Halifax County, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Isle of Wight County, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, James City County-Williamsburg, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, James City County-Williamsburg, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, King and Queen County, 1993
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Lunenburg County, 1993
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Lunenburg County, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Smyth County, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Wise County, 1993 (Folder 1-3)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Wise County, 1993-1994
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Needs and Risk Assessment Project, 1993 (Folder 1-5)
  - St. Gertrude High School (Richmond, Va.), 1989-1990
  - St. John's Hospital (Richmond, Va.), 1989-1993
  - Scott County Board of Supervisors, 1988-1989
  - Scott County Board of Supervisors, 1989-1991
  - ShenanArts, Inc., 1991
  - Southside Community Services Board, 1987-1988
  - Southside Community Services Board, 1988-1990
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1988-1990
  - Sports Virginia, Inc., 1991-1993
  - SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education in Virginia), 1991-1993
  - SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education in Virginia), Substance Abuse Prevention Program, 1993-1994
  - Steamer Co. #5, 1992-1993
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), General, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Accomack County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Alleghany County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Augusta County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Botetourt County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Campbell County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Charles City County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Charlotte County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Charlottesville, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Chesapeake, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Chesterfield County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Clarke County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Clarke County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Cumberland County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Fairfax County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Falls Church, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Fluvanna County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Franklin County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Frederick County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Frederick County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Gloucester County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Greene County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Halifax County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Hampton, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Hanover County, 1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Henrico County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Highland County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), King William County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Lee County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Loudoun County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Lunenburg County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Lynchburg, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Madison County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Madison County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Manassas, 1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Manassas, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Mecklenburg County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Mecklenburg County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Montgomery County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Montgomery County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Nelson County, 1991
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Northampton County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Rappahannock County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Smyth County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Suffolk, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Williamsburg-James City County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Williamsburg-James City County, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Winchester, 1993-1994
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Wise County, 1992
  - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Wise County, 1993-1994
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, General, 1993-1994
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, George Mason University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Germanna Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, James Madison University, 1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Longwood College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Lord Fairfax Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Mary Washington College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Mountain Empire Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Norfolk State University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Old Dominion University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Patrick Henry Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Paul D. Camp Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Piedmont Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Radford University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Thomas Nelson Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, University of Virginia, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia Commonwealth University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia Commonwealth University, Campus Police, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia Highland Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia State University, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia Tech, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Virginia Western Community College, 1993
  - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants, Higher Education, Wytheville Community College, 1993
  - Task Force on Substance Abuse Services for Offenders, 1993
  - This Way House, 1991-1992
  - Tri-County Medical Corp. of Caroline County, 1988-1989
  - UVA, Project Apple, 1993
  - UVA, Special Consultant to the Governor on High Risk Yough, Families, and Communities, 1991-1992
  - UVA, V.I.E.W., 1991-1992
  - UVA, V.I.E.W., 1993
  - Virginia Association of Drug and Alcohol Programs, 1992
  - Virginia Association of Public Television, 1993-1994
  - VCU, Governor's Institute on AOD, 1992
  - VCU, Keeve, Paul W., 1993
  - VCU-MCV, Perinatal Drug Exposure, 1992
  - VCU-VIPD, Amos-Perinatal Substance Abuse Training for Care Givers, 1993
  - VCU-VIDD, Amus, 1993
  - VCU-VIDD, Perinatal Addiction Training Project, 1991-1992
  - VCU-VIDD, Perinatal Addiction Training Project, 1993-1994
  - Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1990
  - Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1990-1992
  - Virginia Federation of Communities for Drug Free Youth, 1993
  - Virginia Heroes, Inc., 1991-1992
  - Virginia Heroes, Inc., 1993
  - Virginia Intervention Education Weekend (V.I.E.W.), 1993
  - Virginia State AFL-CIO, 1991-1992
  - William Byrd Community House, 1988-1989
  - WNVC (Fairfax, Va.), 1990-1991
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #1-6, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #7-10, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #11-18, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #19-25, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #26-33, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #34-39, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #40-42, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #43-53, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #54-60, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #61-65, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #66-67, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #68-70, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #73-78, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #81-89, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, No id #, 1989 July-1991 June
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, Addresses, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #3-25, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #26-40, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #41-50, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #51-70, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #54, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #71-82, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #88-100, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #101-115, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #116-129, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #130-155, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #156-165, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #166-179, 1991 July-1992 September
  - DFSCA, Performance reports, #180-195, 1991 July-1992 September